EMA in technical terms it holds. It's
generally a very strong support. So I
think if at all any weakness persist I
think 24,200 is a level to watch out
for. If at all Nifty comes there I think
it's a good strategy. As I've been
saying do a buy on dips. I know stocks
have been very volatile. One day up two
day down one day up followed by another
crash. So the best strategy I think for
a investor right now is to get into ETFs
in Nifty. do a SIP. These are the levels
to watch for. I think if at all you do a
SIP in Nifty ETFs, I think in the next
three to six months, you'll get
excellent returns on your ETFs. For Bank
Nifty, I think 55,000 is a great
support. It's the 100 day EMA. But
looking at the Nifty, I think if the
weakness persist, I think 54,500 is the
next support level for Bank Nifty. This
is the level where it consolidated and
it I think it broke out towards its
all-time high. So 54,500 is a level to
watch out for Bank Nifty. Overall, both
sectors including your other sectors are
looking quite weak on the charts. So a
buy on dip strategy or a nifty ETF
strategy would be great in the next 3 to
6 months.
>> But Shahin, what is it that you foresee
in the very near term this week? Are we
going to continue to be range? Because
while we have run into six consecutive
weeks of weakness, it's not been one
sharp drop, right? It's been a very gra
create a short position in Vipro. If at
all the market gaps up for any reason
and the stock gaps up, you don't have to
take a short position. Only if it starts
trading below Friday's low, do take a
short position. IT index is looking
quite weak and I think VIPro is about to
break down. So, you can short at current
price uh current levels with a target of
234. Second, ICIC Lombard uh decent uh
fundamental chain 25% month-on-month
premium growth after a decline of two
months and it's holding its 200 day EMA.
It's trading in a very tight
consolidation pattern has given a hammer
on Friday and followed by a good candle
on Thursday. So, I think you can expect
some kind of upside. So, go along ICIC
Lombard with a target of 1974. Please
maintain your stop loss in the system of
1854 on a daily closing basis.
Okay, so those are the picks that Sharon
is liking this morning. On that note,
we'll slip into a very short break and
come back. Keep the discussion going
about all the stocks to watch out
possibly be right back.
[Music]